<biblScope>47</biblScope>
and drives the Negros, men and women without distinction, as he would drive horses or cattle in a team. <persName key="Cooper, ?" from="?" to="?" role="Slave Overseer" ref="?">Mr. Cooper</persName>does not say that <persName key="Cooper, ?" from="?" to="?" role="Slave Overseer" ref="?">he </persName> is always using the whip, but it is known to be always present, and ready to be applied to the back or shoulders of any who flag at their work, or lag behind the line*. The driver, who is generaly a Black man, has the power not only of thus stimulating the slaves under him to exertion, by the application of the whip to their bodies while they are proceeding with their work; but, when he consideres any of them to have committed a fault deserving of a more serious notice, he has the power also of prostrating them (women as well as men) on the ground, causing them to be firmly held down by other Negros, who grasp the hands and legs of their prostrate companion, when he may inflict upon the bare postriors such a number of lashes as he may deem the fault to have merited; the whole number may he which inflict at one time, without the presence of the overseer, being, by the Slave Act of 1816, limited to 10. One of the faults which the driver most frequently punishes in this way, is that of coming too late to the feild either in the morning or after dinner. Those who arrive after the fixed time are pretty sure to get a few, perhaps five or six lashes. <persName key="Cooper, ?" from="?" to="?" role="Slave Overseer" ref="?"> Mr. Cooper</persName>, on one occasion, saw three or four old women come too late; they knew they were to be whipped, and as soon as they came up through themselves down on the ground to receive the lashes; some of them received four, others six lashes. These minor punnishments, <persName key="Cooper, ?" from="?" to="?" role="Slave Overseer" ref="?"> Mr. Cooper </persName>says, are very freequent. <persName key="Cooper, ?" from="?" to="?" role="Slave Overseer" ref="?">He</persName>  beleives that seldom a day passes without some occuring; and <persName key="Cooper, ?" from="?" to="?" role="Slave Overseer" ref="?">he</persName> has heard of as many as sixty Negros being flogged in one morning for being late. </p>
<p> More serious punishments are only inflicted by the authority of the overseer; and the mode of their infliction is usually the same as has been already described. Whether the offender be male or female, precicely the same course is pursued. The posteriors are made bare, and the offender is extended prone on the ground, the hans and feet being firmly held and extended by the other slaves; when the driver, with his long and heavy whip, inflicts, under the <p> * In one of his printed letters, in which he is replying to an objection, <persName key="Cooper, ?" from="?" to="?" role="Slave Overseer" ref="?"> Mr. Cooper</persName> incidentally but very significantly remarks, that "to a Jamaca man" it would be truly astonishing "to learn that the whip was not needed, or that its sound was rarely heard."

























</body></text></TEI></teiCorpus>